With everything you've learned,
凭你到目前为止所学的
you're just about ready to
你应当到了
tackle your first programming assignment.
可以开始攻克第一个编程作业的时候了
Before you do that,
在动手之前
let me just give you a quick tour
让我为你快速介绍一下
of ipython notebooks in Coursera.
Coursera上的iPython notebook工具
Here you see,Jupiter iphython notebooks
这就是Jupiter ipython界面
that you can get to in Coursera.
你可以从Coursera中打开它
Let me just quickly show you a few features of this.
让我简短给展示一下它的一些功能
The instructions are written right here in the text in the
这个notebook的用法就写在这里
iPython notebook and these little
写在了文字区域内 而这下面的
light grey blocks are blocks of code.
这些浅灰色的框 则是代码框
So occasionally, you see in these blocks, sometimes they'll say
有时你能看到在这些浅灰色的块中写着
this is the "START CODE HERE" and "END CODE HERE".
"代码开始处" 与 "代码终止处"
To do the programming exercise, please make sure to write your code
当做编程作业时 请确保你把代码
between the "START CODE HERE" and "END CODE HERE".
都写在这两行字之间
so for example print "Hello World"
比如我写代码印出 "Hello World"
Then to execute a code block
如果要执行一个代码框中的代码
You can hit Shift+Enter,
你可以按 Shift+Enter
And then to execute this code block
所以我们执行一下这行
which I guess we just wrote print "Hello World",
就是刚才写的 print "Hello World"
So that printed "Hello World".
于是它就印出了"Hello World"
To run a cell --- run one of these code blocks or a "cell", you can also
如果想运行一个Cell -- Cell是代码框的别称
click "Cell", and then "Run Cell" so it executes this.
你也可以点击 Cell 然后点 Run Cell 就会执行这个代码框
It's possible that on your computer the
也许在你的电脑上
keyboard shortcut for Cell/Run Cell
Cell 里的 Run Cell 的快捷键
might be different than Shift+Enter,
可能不是 Shift+Enter
but on both my Mac as well as on my PC
但是在我的苹果电脑和我的普通电脑上
it's Shift+Enter so it might be the same for you as well.
快捷键都是 Shift+Enter 所以可能你也是一样吧
Now when you read the instructions, if you accidentally
如果你在阅读说明时一不小心双击了代码框
double-click on it you may end up with this Markdown language.
它可能会变成 Markdown 语言
If you end up with this funny-looking text, to convert it
如果你的代码突然变成了这种奇怪的文字
to the nice-looking text, just run the cell, so
只要运行一下这个框就能变回来
you'd click the Cell, Run Cell, or I'm gonna hit Shift+Enter,
所以你可以点 Cell 再点 Run Cell 或按 Shift+Enter
and that basically executes the Markdown and turns it back
这实际上把Markdown当作了代码执行
to this nice looking code.
也就变成了正常的文字
Just a couple more tips, when you execute code like this,
再提示几点 这些你所执行的代码
it actually runs on a kernel,
实际上是运行在一个内核(kernel)中的
or a piece of code that runs on a server,
也就是在某台服务器上运行的一段代码
If it's running an excessively large job,
如果这个内核的运算量非常大的话
or if you leave the computer for a very long time,
或者你离开电脑很长时间
or something goes wrong, your internet connection or something,
或者出了什么意外 譬如你断网了之类的
there is a small chance that the kernel in the back end may die,
会有小机率导致这些在后端运行的内核意外终止
in which case just click Kernel,
这种情况下 只要点击 Kernel
and then Restart Kernel and hopefully, that will reboot the kernel
然后再点 Restart Kernel 这样应该就能重启内核
and make it work again. That shouldn't happen
并将它恢复了 这种情形不应该发生在
if you're just running relatively small jobs and
你运行的运算任务都很小的情况下
just starting up your iPython notebook,
或是你的 notebook 才刚刚开启的情况下
if you see an error message that
不过如果你看到了错误消息
the kernel has died or something, you can try
说内核终止或之类的情况
Kernel, Restart. Finally, in an iPython
你可以试着重启内核 最后的一点提示是
notebook like this, there may be multiple
在像这样的 iPython notebook 中 可能会
blocks of code, so even if an earlier block of code
有很多的代码框 而有的靠前的代码框中
doesn't have any graded code,
可能没有任何会需要打分的代码
be sure to execute this block of code
但也务必执行它们
because in this example,
因为在这个例子中
it imports numpy as np and so on,
这个代码把 numpy 程序库导入为了 np
and sets some variables you'll need
还设定了一些你之后需要的变量
in order to execute the lower-down blocks of code.
有了这些变量你才能执行接下来的代码
So be sure to execute the ones on top,
所以请务必执行前面的代码
even if you aren't asked to write any code in them.
哪怕你没有被要求在其中写任何代码也要如此
And finally when you're done implementing your solutions
当你最终把解法实现完成时
there's this blue submit assignment button
这里有一个蓝色的提交作业按钮
here on the right, and we click that, and
位于界面右侧 只需点一下它
we'll submit your solutions for grading.
你的解答就会被提交并评分
I found that the interactive
我发现由于iPython notebook
command shell nature of iPython notebooks
本质上是一个交互式命令外壳(shell)
is very useful for letting you quickly implement
因此它对于快速实现代码非常有用
a few lines of code, see an outcome,
你可以写几行代码 就立即观察到结果
learn to iterate very quickly, and so I hope that
也可以学习快速迭代 所以我希望
the programming exercises in the Coursera Jupyter iPython notebooks
Coursera上的Jupyter iPython notebook编程作业
will help you to quickly learn, experiment and see
能够帮助你快速学习 尝试 并且理解
how to implement these learning algorithms.
如何实现这些深度学习算法
There's one more video after this that's an optional video,
在这个可选视频之后还有一个视频
that talks about the cost function of Logistic regression,
它讨论的内容是逻辑回归中的代价函数
you can watch that or not, either way is perfectly fine,
你看或不看都可以 都完全没有关系
but either way, best of luck with the
但无论如何 都祝你好运
week 2 programming assignments
祝你顺利完成第二周的编程作业
and I also look forward to seeing you
我也很期待能够
at the start of the week 3 materials.
在第三周的课程开始时再次见到你